<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fun TV Facts</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="tvshow_name_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="tvshow_name_himym">How I Met Your Mother</string>
    <string name="tvshow_name_got">Game Of Thrones</string>
    <string name="tvshow_name_2_and_a_half_men">2 And a Half Men</string>
    <string name="tvshow_name_tbbt">The Big Bang Theory</string>

    <string name="prev_button_text">Prev</string>
    <string name="next_button_text">Next</string>



    <string name="tvshow_friends_fun_fact_1"><b>THE SHOW WAS ORIGINALLY CALLED INSOMNIA CAFÉ ... AND A BUNCH OF OTHER THINGS.</b> \n\nIn the early \'90s, the creators of Friends, David Crane and Marta Kauffman, wrote a seven-page pitch for Insomnia Café. \n\nIn addition to the different title, the plot itself was quite different from what we know as Friends. For example, Ross and Rachel weren\'t the key relationship. Instead, Joey and Monica were supposed to be love interests.\n\nAfter NBC bought the pilot, the title became Friends Like Us. NBC president Warren Littlefield came up with another title that was also considered, Across the Hall. By the time they shot it, the title had switched again to Six of One. When the show premiered on September 22, 1994, they had finally landed on simply Friends.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_friends_fun_fact_2"><b>THEY WERE THE FIRST TV CAST TO NEGOTIATE AS A GROUP.</b>\n\nDuring the first season, they were each receiving around $22,000 per episode. But allegedly, by the second season, each actor had a slightly different salary.\n\nIn 1997, all six cast members refused to work until they all earned an equal salary of $100,000 per episode. This was big news. The New York Times reported, “Stars of hit shows often threaten to boycott their series in pursuit of higher salaries. \n\nWhat is unusual is this cast\'s effort to use solidarity as leverage.This negotiation worked very well. By the final season, each cast member was earning $1 million per episode.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_friends_fun_fact_3"><b>THE ROLE OF ROSS WAS WRITTEN FOR DAVID SCHWIMMER</b>\n\nThis may come as a surprise because Eric McCormack, the Will of Will &amp; Grace, made news when he said that he auditioned “two or three times” for Ross. \n\nBut, executive producer Kevin Bright had worked with Schwimmer before, so the writers were already developing Ross\’s character in Schwimmer\’s voice. And indeed, Schwimmer was the first person cast on the show.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_friends_fun_fact_4"><b>THE CAST HAD A HUDDLE BEFORE EVERY EPISODE.</b>\n\nEvery week before filming commenced, the cast would get together for a moment to prepare for the show. This was the moment that David Schwimmer was dreading before the finale because he knew it would make him emotional. \n\n“I started to lose it in this ritual that we had before the show," he said, "which is just a group hug, kind of get in a little circle, right before we come out. And that was the moment I was dreading for a long time because I knew that moment of just looking at everyone in their eyes, and saying \'Have a good show,\' and knowing that was the last time we were going to be able to be in our little circle.”</string>
    <string name="tvshow_friends_fun_fact_5"><b>MANY PEOPLE, INCLUDING LISA KUDROW, THOUGHT THAT CHANDLER WAS GAY.</b>\n\nKudrow said that she was surprised to hear Perry’s interpretation of Chandler at the first table read because when she first read the script, she thought Chandler was supposed to be gay. And she wasn’t the only one. \n\nDuring the first few seasons of the show, many fans speculated about Chandler\'s sexual orientation. In 1997, David Crane told Entertainment Weekly, “No, Chandler isn\'t gay. Nor will he be gay.”</string>

    <string name="tvshow_himym_fun_fact_1"><b>NNEIL PATRICK HARRIS IS REALLY A TALENTED MAGICIAN.</b>\n\nHe is the president of The Magic Castle Club in Los Angeles.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_himym_fun_fact_2"><b>TED, MARSHALL, AND LILY ARE BASED ON REAL PEOPLE.</b>\n\nWhen college friends and Late Show with David Letterman writers Carter Bays and Craig Thomas were invited to pitch a network series, they flashed back to 1997, when Bays spent a lot of his time at Thomas\'s apartment, which he shared with his longtime girlfriend (now-wife) Rebecca, complaining about about being single.\n\nIn the script, Bays became Ted, Thomas became Marshall, and Rebecca became Lily. Real-life moments like Bays inviting someone to a wedding without realizing he didn’t have a plus-one, or calling Rebecca a “bitch” during a brief breakup with Thomas were written into the series.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_himym_fun_fact_3"><b>BRITNEY SPEARS WANTED TO BE ON THE SHOW.</b>\n\nSpecifically on the episode “Ten Sessions,” which freaked out Bays and Thomas, who were worried that the singer would want to play Stella, a character for whom they had big plans. Instead she liked the role of Stella\'s receptionist, Abby. \n\nThe episode was the most-watched episode at that point in the 18-to-49 year old demographic, and was credited with possibly saving the show from cancellation.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_himym_fun_fact_4"><b>TED\'S KIDS KNEW THE ENDING OF THE SERIES FOR NINE YEARS.</b>\n\nLyndsy Fonseca (Penny) and David Henrie (Luke) shot all of their scenes during season one, because Henrie was going through puberty. When the kids\'s footage for the series finale was shot, Thomas and Bays were the only people present. \n\nFonseca and Henrie also had to sign a confidentiality agreement. The two honored it, even after Henrie was bribed with alcohol at bars by strangers wanting to know what he did.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_himym_fun_fact_5"><b>JOSH RADNOR KEPT THE BLUE FRENCH HORN.</b>\n\nBays and Thomas agreed to split custody of the iconic prop, but the actor who played Ted Mosby “humbly and sweetly” asked for it. "And folks, when Ted Mosby comes and asks you for the blue French horn, ya give him the blue French horn," Thomas said. "It felt right." \n\nNeil Patrick Harris took home Barney’s playbook and the group’s MacLaren’s tabletop, Smulders got Robin Sparkles’s denim jacket, and Hannigan acquired the little British phone booth.</string>

    <string name="tvshow_got_fun_fact_1"><b>THE AVERAGE EPISODE COSTS HBO $6 MILLION TO MAKE.</b>\n\nGame of Thrones is one of most expensive shows on TV. It costs three times as much to make an episode of GoT as it does to make an episode of The Big Bang Theory. (However, it is still costs $1 million less than it did to make any episode on the final season of Friends).\r\n\r\nSome GoT episodes cost even more than $6 million to make. Season 2\'s action-packed \"Blackwater\" skated in with a reported price tag of $8 million.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_got_fun_fact_2"><b>PETER DINKLAGE THOUGHT THE SHOW HAD BEEN CANCELLED.</b>\n\nAfter the pilot was picked up, David Benioff pranked Peter Dinklage by calling him and telling him the show had been cancelled. It was six hours before Dinklage learned otherwise.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_got_fun_fact_3"><b>SANSA STARK ADOPTED HER DIREWOLF IN REAL LIFE.</b>\n\nSophie Turner, who plays Sansa Stark, adopted Zunni, the Northern Inuit dog that played her pet direwolf on the series\u2019 first season. \u201CGrowing up I always wanted a dog, but my parents never wanted one,\u201D Turner told Coventry Telegraph in 2013. \u201CWe kind of fell in love with my character\u2019s direwolf, Lady, on set. We knew Lady died and they wanted to re-home her. My mum persuaded them to let us adopt her.\u201D</string>
    <string name="tvshow_got_fun_fact_4"><b>SHOOTING THE HORSE HEART SCENE WAS AN UNPLEASANT EXPERIENCE.</b>\n\nThe horse heart Daenerys had to eat in season one was essentially a giant gummy candy\u2014one that, per Clarke, tasted a little bit like bleach. To make the proceedings even grosser, all the fake blood made Clarke so sticky that she got stuck to a toilet.\r\n</string>
    <string name="tvshow_got_fun_fact_5"><b>RAMSAY SNOW ALMOST PLAYED JON SNOW.</b>\n\nIwan Rheon was the runner-up to play Jon Snow. The role went to Kit Harington, and Rheon went on to play Roose Bolton\u2019s sadistic bastard son, Ramsay, instead.</string>

    <string name="tvshow_2andahalf_fun_fact_1"><b>CHARLIE WAS PAID, A LOT!</b>\n\nIn 2008 Charlie Sheen was earning $300,000 per episode. By 2011 he was being paid $1.8 million per episode, making him the highest paid actor on TV at the time</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2andahalf_fun_fact_2"><b>CHARLIE\'S TROUBLES</b>\n\nThroughout the series, Sheen interrupted the filming because of rehabilitation, public remarks again the producers\/show\u2019s network, and various other issues. \n\nIn 2008 he was confirmed to be one of the highest paid actors on television and eventually reached the point of earning $1.8 million for a single episode. In 2011, it was officially announced that Sheen wouldn\u2019t be coming back for another season.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2andahalf_fun_fact_3"><b>BERTA ORIGINALLY DID NOT HAVE A PERMANENT ROLE.</b>\n\nConchata Ferrel was originally only meant to appear in a recurring role capacity but she became such an instant hit with the audience that the curmudgeonly Berta was written into almost every episode.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2andahalf_fun_fact_4"><b>ASHTON KUTCHER DID UNDERWEAR MODELLING.</b>\n\nAshton Kutcher, who replaced Sheen on the show, was said in one episode to be an underwear model. In real life, Kutcher had once modeled underwear, and he also got a job modeling underwear in one episode of \u2018That 70s Show\u2019. </string>
    <string name="tvshow_2andahalf_fun_fact_5"><b>CHARLIE COULD NOT PLAY THE PIANO.</b>\n\nIn the series that used to star Charlie Sheen, his character wrote jingles on the piano and sung. You would be surprised to know that Sheen couldn’t actually play and Dennis C.Brown composed all the jingles while Sheen’s character pretended to play the piano. </string>

    <string name="tvshow_tbbt_fun_fact_1"><b>\'SOFT KITTY\' IS AN ACTUAL SONG</b>\n\n\'Soft Kitty\' is the only thing that can help Sheldon feel better on the rare occasions he is ill, but did you know that it exists outside the show? Sort of.\n\nThe song dates back to the 1930s, and was titled \'Warm Kitty\' by Edith Newlin. Producer Bill Prady revealed that his daughter sang \'Soft Kitty\' while at pre-school, after her teacher first heard it while working in Australia.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_tbbt_fun_fact_2"><b>THE CAST ARE ALSO HIGHLY SKILLED MUSICIANS</b>\n\nAside from being academic geeks, most of the characters are also talented musicians. To achieve this, three of the stars are actually highly skilled themselves.\n\nJohnny Galecki has been a cellist from a young age, while Jim Parsons and Mayim Bialik learned how to play the theremin and the harp especially for the show.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_tbbt_fun_fact_3"><b>WE STILL DON\'T KNOW PENNY\'S SURNAME</b>\n\nUnlike the other characters, Penny is the only one whose surname has never been revealed. Reports claim that Kaley Cuoco Sweeting prefers to keep this a mystery throughout the whole series.\n\nCo-creator Bill Prady has said that the name will be revealed eventually, but producer Steve Molaro has said the opposite, so who knows. Unless of course her name is Penny Penny Penny, and Sheldon\'s knocks make more sense.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_tbbt_fun_fact_4"><b>ACTRESS MAYIM BIALIK HAS AN ACTUAL NEUROSCIENCE PHD IN REAL LIFE</b>\n\nAmy Farrah Fowler is one smart lady, but it turns out that actress Mayim Bialik is pretty darn smart too. In 2007, she earned a PhD in neuroscience studies. After filming Blossom as a child, she attended UCLA having been accepted at Harvard and Yale.\r\n\r\nShe also earned a BS degree in neuroscience, Hebrew studies and Jewish studies. Her dissertation was an investigation of hypothalamic activity in patients with Prader\u2013Willi syndrome, titled \'Hypothalamic regulation in relation to maladaptive, obsessive-compulsive, affiliative, and satiety behaviors in Prader-Willi syndrome\'. Woah.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_tbbt_fun_fact_5"><b>NEARLY EVERYONE HAS SEEN PENNY NAKED.</b>\n\nDespite being the first to flirt with her, Howard is the only one of the male characters not to see Penny naked at some time or another.\n\nLeonard has obviously seen her naked many times, while Raj had a one-night-sort-of-stand and Sheldon helped Penny to the hospital after she fell in the shower.</string>

</resources>
